veritaspress.com 2019-05-18

# Veritas Press | Privacy Policy

Veritas Press is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our websites. This privacy policy outlines how we collect information when you visit one of our sites, how we use that information, and how you can update it.

## Information We Collect

We collect various types of information from our website visitors so we can adjust our websites to meet our users' needs and expectations. Some of this information is collected automatically and other information is provided by site users.

**Information collected automatically**

We collect limited information your browser makes available when visiting websites. This information, which helps us assess the effectiveness of our websites, includes:

  * Your Internet Protocol address
  * The Browser type (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.)
  * Your computer’s operating system (Windows, Macintosh, etc.)
  * Your Internet domain (AOL, Earthlink, etc.)
  * URLs of the websites you come to our websites from
  * The pages on our website that you visit
  * Your country, territory, or region

In some instances, our websites use cookies that uniquely identify your browser so that we may provide content most relevant to your needs. While you may disable cookies on your computer, this may result in our services not working correctly for you.

## Information you provide to us

You provide information to Veritas when you fill out online forms on our websites or use a login-required service. Depending on the type of the service, we use your information in different ways as outlined below.

## Inquiry and application forms

Your contact information (phone, mailing address, and/or email) is used to contact you to provide information about the school or curriculum, including sales of additional materials and/or courses.

If you do not wish to provide your contact information online, call us and request that information be sent through the mail.

## Purchasing merchandise

Your contact information is used to send merchandise to you, and to provide information if necessary.

Your financial information is used for billing.

If you do not wish to provide your contact or financial information online, you may call Veritas to place an order.

## Login sites and services

Various websites and web services of Veritas Press, Veritas Press Scholars Academy, and VeritasBible.com require users to log in to gain access to information and tools reserved for students, faculty and staff.

## Our security measures

Our websites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting your credit card information during the online ordering process, as well as whenever we ask you to log in to any of the Veritas’ online accounts.

## Your Privacy

Veritas Press does not share your personal information to any outside organizations. Veritas will abide by all applicable laws governing the release of personal information.

Collective information about site users – but never individuals’ information – is used in marketing, advertising and other relationships with third parties.

## COPPA notice

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, or COPPA, applies to the collection of personal information from children under 13. Veritas Press ([www.veritaspress.com](http://www.veritaspress.com/) & [www.veritasbible.com](http://www.veritasbible.com/)) offers programs for students in grades K-12. It collects personal identifying information through its inquiry and application forms. Veritas Press realizes that children may occasionally fill out and submit these forms.

Parents may ask to have the child’s personal identifying information deleted by using the contact information below.

**Website operator:**  
Veritas Press  
1805 Olde Homestead Lane  
Lancaster, PA 17601  
(800) 922 5082  

## How we use this information

Veritas Press uses information collected automatically to better understand the needs of website visitors so that we may improve our websites and services.

Information you provide may be used by for marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive marketing emails or phone calls, you may use the opt-out feature on our emails or call Veritas at (800) 922 5082.

## How to update your information

Our student and faculty services site provide you with the option of changing and modifying information you have previously provided to us.

## Changes to this policy

Veritas Press reserves the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We expect any such changes to be minor, and notification of all changes will be made on this page. Each version of the Privacy Policy will be dated at the bottom of the page.
